* Resources
* About Us

* Resources
* About Us

Jupiter Privacy Policy Snapshot
===============================

We will uphold your trust in us by protecting and using your Personal Information in a responsible manner. Every day, we continue to reimagine banking experiences for all the ways you live, and it's no coincidence that your Personal Information plays a big role in making all that happen. We value your trust and aim to be transparent in the ways we use your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to keep creating banking that fits into your lives effortlessly - so you can truly live more and bank less. Read the full Privacy Policy document here for more information [(Link to the complete document)](https://jupiter.money/privacy-policy-detail).

What type of Personal Information do we collect?
------------------------------------------------

We want you to understand the types of information that we collect, so you can then make the best decisions about what you share with us. Personal Information will inter alia include any information which is directly or indirectly available with us to identify or verify individual identity. This may also include sensitive personal data which inter alia includes financial information such as bank account, credit and debit card details, biometric information when you interact with our products or services.

#### Categories of Personal Information we may collect:

* Identity and Account Opening Information (e.g. name, address, date of birth)
* Contact Information (e.g. mobile number, permanent/shipping address)
* Financial Information (e.g. Bank account number)
* Identification Information (e.g. KYCs, PAN number)
* Transactional Information (Money Flow) (e.g. UPI ID)
* Usage and Technical Information (e.g. IP address)
* Credit and Lending Information (e.g. credit score)
* Marketing and Communication Information (e.g. customer support logs)
* Information in your device(s) (e.g. camera, contact list)

How do we collect your Personal Information?
--------------------------------------------

Any personal information held by us will be committed to a high degree of protection.

We process/collect data received (a) directly from you through Jupiter Platforms or through different communication channels or the services or product you entail to use and when you provide your details in forms, surveys, online applications or similar online fields (b) indirectly from third party sources including but not limited to credit institution companies, market research, publicly available information, payment gateway companies, business partners, financial institutions.

How do we use your Personal Information?
----------------------------------------

Your Personal Information allows us to create more personalised and unique banking experiences just for you. When you trust us with your data, it's only right that you understand how we may use it:

#### For General Support

Verify your identity before providing our services, or responding to any of your queries, applications, feed-back and complaints

#### For Our Internal Operations

* Aid our research and analysis, so that we keep improving our services, products and advertising strategies.
* Manage our day-to-day business operations.
* Ensure that the information we have about you is up-to-date.
* Comply with all laws and obligations from any legal authorities.
* Seek professional advice, including legal.
* Update you on changes to our products or services that you might be currently engaged in.
* Performing necessary checks strictly within the scope of providing the app's intended services, such as identity verification to prevent fraud and/or for ensuring compliance with legal and regulatory obligations directly related to the services provided through Jupiter Platform.

#### For Marketing Purposes

Contact you and offer products or services that you might be interested in (via EDMs, direct mailers, SMS-es, phone calls, social media, 3rd party sites, etc)

Who do we share your Personal Information with?
-----------------------------------------------

To deliver on our promise of helping you to live more, we often partner up with third parties, Partner Banks that bring you rewards or promotions or partner us to provide you product and services that give you more out of life. We may also from time to time, share your Personal Information with others to keep improving your banking experiences with us but always in a responsible manner:

#### Who?

* Third parties such as campaign partners and vendors who work with us (in India or elsewhere)
* Carefully selected business partner or Partner Banks to introduce you to products and services you might be interested in.
* Relevant authorities such as government or law enforcement agencies or regulators.

#### How?

* We require all personnel of Jupiter and third parties to ensure that any of your data disclosed to them is kept confidential and secure through legally enforceable arrangements.
* We may process your data outside of India subject to applicable data protection laws.
* We do not sell your Personal Information to any third parties and we shall comply fully with any duty or obligation of confidentiality that governs our relationship with you.

What rights you have regarding your Personal Information?
---------------------------------------------------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Access to your information | You may request record of your Personal Information being processed by us, upon the verification of your identity and other information as per the Company internal policy |
| Review, Correct and Rectify your information | You may review, correct or rectify the inaccurate Personal Information that is stored with us |
| Withdrawing your consent | (a)You may withdraw a consent to processing that you have given us and prevent further processing of your Personal Information subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy; (b) You may also withhold your consent prior to the collection and processing of your combined information |

You can exercise any of the aforementioned rights by submitting a request to [privacy@jupiter.money](mailto:privacy@jupiter.money); These rights are limited in some situations, such as, where we are legally or otherwise bound to process or retain your Personal Information. This may also affect our ability to provide you service and therefore may lead to discontinuation of the Service you procure from Jupiter.

### Talk to Us

To speak to us regarding our privacy practices (including for any correction or access request), you may write to our Grievance Officer Mr. Rajesh R Singh, Amica Financial Technologies Private Limited.

e-mail ID: - [privacy@jupiter.money](mailto:privacy@jupiter.money)

### Find out more

We may amend our policy from time to time to ensure consistency with any developments to the way Jupiter uses your data. We will make the updated policy available on our website.

More from Jupiter

[

#### Co-created community

We’re building Jupiter hand-in-hand with users like you. Envision the bank you would want to be a part of.](https://community.jupiter.money/)[

#### Demystifying your money

Fun filled insights from FinForAll by Jupiter helps you make smarter financial decisons](https://jupiter.money/resources/finforall-by-jupiter/)

New age banking demands [transparent terms and conditions](https://jupiter.money/terms-and-conditions/)

No fine prints on Jupiter. Simple to understand [fees and charges.](https://jupiter.money/fees-rates-charges/)

Check us out on our socials

* ABOUT

* PRODUCTS
* [Edge Federal Bank  
    Credit Card](https://jupiter.money/edge-credit-card/)
* [Edge CSB Bank  
    Credit Card](https://jupiter.money/edge-upi-credit-card/)

* CALCULATORS

* RESOURCES

* USEFUL LINKS

* ABOUT +
* PRODUCTS +
* CALCULATORS +
* RESOURCES +
* USEFUL LINKS +

| Products on our Platform | Role of Partner |
| --- | --- |
| Bank and Deposit Accounts | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter has partnered with Federal bank to offer Savings Bank accounts, Fixed and Recurring Deposits to consumers. |
| Cards | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter is a marketplace which promotes co-branded cards distributed by Europa Neo Marketing Pvt Ltd in partnership with Federal Bank & CSB Bank. Cards are issued by the bank as per policy of the bank. |
| Loans | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter has partnered with the following NBFC’s [Amica Finance Private Limited](https://www.jupiter.credit/) & Kisetsu Saison Finance (India) Private Limited to provide lending products to consumers. |
| Mutual Funds | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter has partnered with AIAPL to provide mutual funds to consumers |
| Digital Gold | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter has partnered with MMTC-PAMP to provide Digital Gold products to consumers. |
| Health Insurance | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter has partnered with Onsurity to provide Health Insurance Products to consumers. |
| Gift Cards | AFTPL through its brand Jupiter has partnered with Pine Labs to provide Pre Paid Gift Card Products to consumers. |

We work with trusted partners

Jupiter deploys high level security standards to keep your money safe

##### SECURITY PARTNERS

##### BANKING AND PAYMENT PARTNERS

The savings account, bank deposits and cobranded VISA Debit Card are issued by Federal Bank - a scheduled commercial bank. All funds in the account are insured up to approved limits by DICGC. Your Savings Account and bank deposits are hosted by our partner bank and follows all security standards prescribed by the bank/regulator. Co-branded Credit Cards : AFTPL through its brand Jupiter is a marketplace and promotes co-branded cards distributed by Europa Neo Marketing Pvt Ltd in partnership with the following issuers: Federal Bank and CSB Bank. Approval of your credit card application is subject to issuer banks eligibility criteria. 'Jupiter' itself is not a bank and doesn't hold or claim to hold a banking license. Your money is always safe with our partner bank. Amica Investment Advisers Private Limited, is a SEBI registered Investment Adviser - INA000015507 and an AMFI Registered CAT-1 Execution only Platform (EOP) with registration number CAT-1 EOP-0005. Mutual Funds investments are subject to market risks, read all scheme related documents carefully. Past performance is not an indicator for future returns.

© Amica Financial Technologies Private Limited.

✕

##### 3-in-1 Switch RuPay Credit Card

Lifetime Free

2% cashback

Pay on UPI with Credit Card

Powerd by Issued by
